tell me at least one product that
скажите мне хоть один товар который
Russia sells to the world besides
Россия продаёт в мир кроме
raw materials, let's think, do
сырья ну давайте подумаем давайте
you have any options, no,
у вас есть какие-то вариант нету
hello,
здравствуйте
good evening, where are you
добрый вечер вы откуда
from, Ivanovo, it's
из Иванова
funny, what do you think, the United
прикольно как вы считаете Соединённые
States, friend or foe,
Штаты друг враг
who is
кому
your
вам
enemy, enemy, I understand, but why is it that if it's an enemy, then
враг враг понял а почему же если враг то
now Russia is just fawning over the
сейчас Россия прямо аж лебезит перед
United States,
Соединёнными Штатами
how is it expressed, well, for
как это выражается
example, Putin proposed to Trump to
ну вот например Путин предложил Трампу
develop the Arctic together, proposed to
вместе Арктику разрабатывать предложил
mine aluminum in Russia, the Americans need
алюминий добывать в России американцам
money,
деньги нужны
that is, well, it turns out that you sell
то есть ну за деньги получается продаёте
resources for money, yes, you get them, uh, as a raw materials appendage of the
ресурсы да достаёте ээ сырьвым придатком
West, as I understand it,
Запада я так понял
Ukraine sells money and
деньги продаёт Украина и свои ресурсы
Ukraine sells its resources, no, it's clear with Ukraine,
продаёт Украина нет так с Украиной
Ukraine is like there, that's under Europe, that's under America, but why did Russia lie down under America, it lay down under America, well, how did it not lie down, it offers, yes, that the Americans extract resources from them for cheap and export them when the nineties began and after that Putin came, all this, as
пришёл после этого Путин вот эту всю как
you say, selling resources for
ты рассказываешь продажи ресурсов за
pennies, Putin
копейки Путин
closed down and if  we will sell our
прикрыл и если мы будем продавать свои
resources our land then we will sell
ресурсы своей земли то будем продавать
for good money and not for pennies and not for
за хорошие деньги а не за копейки и
nothing for their debts to Ukraine well
недаром за свои долги в Украину
I just can't understand why
ну просто я не могу понять вот почему
Russia instead of doing what
Россия вместо того что вот как делает
America does it extracts resources everywhere
Америка она добывает увсюду ресурсы
produces high-tech things and
производит высокотехнологические вещи и
sells them back at three times the price yes for
продаёт назад в три дорого да вот
example it will take aluminum from Russia
например будет забирать у России
and produce
алюминий да производить ложки
aluminum spoons and sell them to
алюминиевые и продавать
Russia yes and why does Russia
России да а почему Рос почему Россия
not produce anything but only trades
ничего не производит а только торгует
its resources cheaply to America this is the fact that it is a
дёшево Америке своими ресурсами это ж
raw material appendage of the West yes
есть то что сырьевой придаток Запада да
aluminum in Rus' in Russia in Rus' as
алюминий на Руси в России на Руси как
you like it is sold perfectly both in the
вам нравится продаётся прекрасно и в
form of just metal and in the form of products
виде просто металла и в виде изделий
that are necessary for the production
которые необходимы для производства
for example of the same windows the same
например тех же самых окон тех же самых
profiles there I don't know anything is
профилей там не знаю всё что угодно это
produced in Russia in elevator
производится в России на лифтейных
factories all this is perfectly processed
заводах всё это прекрасно обрабатывается
produced and delivered to the end
производится и поставляется конечному
buyer
покупателю
so if you if someone wants to buy
вот если вы если кто-то хочет купить
finished aluminum as a raw material please
готовый алюминий как сырьё пожалуйста
buy but buy not for pennies not for
покупайте но покупайте не за копейки не
debts but for money yeah these are normal
за долги а за деньги угу это нормальные
economic relations normal
экономические отношения нормальные
economic relations
экономические отношения
yazhuni I will tell you  I sell I sell not for
яжуни я вам его продаю продаю не
free I understand correctly that
бесплатно понял я правильно понимаю что
Russia sells only raw materials to the West
Россия на Запад продаёт только сырьё
not only raw materials why what does Russia sell to the
не только сырьё почему что продаёт на
West
запад Россия
well I don't deal with these issues but I
ну я не занимаюсь этими вопросами но я
think that they sell the
думаю что продают то же
same thing how to count wheat is a raw material raw materials raw materials
самое как считать пшеница - это сырьё
wheat is a raw material yes I don't
сырьё сырьё пшеница - это сырьё да я не
think raw materials you can google yes it is a
думаю сырьё можете загуглить да это
raw material bakery products are no longer raw materials and
сырьё хлебобулочные изделия - это уже не
wheat is a raw material well let it be raw materials yes it
сырьё а пшеница - это сырьё ну пускай
sells raw materials sells
будет сырьё да продаёт сырьё продаёт
oil sells gas these are all raw materials that is
нефть продаёт газ это всё сырьё то есть
oil is also a raw material yes that is it turns out
нефть тоже сырьё да то есть получается
that Russia is a raw material appendage of the West
что Россия сырьевой придаток Запада
why but it just supplies the West with raw materials there is
почему но она просто поставляет Западу
nothing like that well except for
сырьё нет ничего подобного да ну кроме
raw materials it produces nothing
сырья ничего она не производит такого
that the Ministry of Foreign Affairs sells well okay but the
что продаёт мид ну хорошо но тот же
same space if we touch we will touch
самый космос если мы касаться касаться
space not a single engine space does not go
будем космоса ни один двигатель космос
without Russia again not a single
не уходит без России ещё раз ни один ээ
ship that rises into space with a
корабль который поднимается в космос с
heavy load does not go without
большой нагрузкой не уходит без
Russian engines for example an engine so
двигателей России например двигатель так
again American and Chinese  launches
ещё раз американские и китайские запуски
and European into space all on Russian
и европейские в космос всё на российских
engines not all but most of them can't do
двигателях не всё но большая часть они
without it they buy
без этого не могут они покупают
Russian engines with which they
российские двигатели с которых они
rise into
поднимаются в
space did you know about this no this is the first time I'm
космос вы об этом и знали нет впервые
listening can you show me some data like that that
слушаю можете мне где-то показать данные
is do I understand correctly that
такие то есть я правильно понимаю что
Elon Musk's Space X buys
Space X Илона Маска закупает в России
engines for its rockets in Russia no
двигатели для своих ракет да нет
satellites and rockets and heavy cargo are
спутники и ракеты и тяжёлые груз - это
completely different things and without this there would be no
совершенно другие вещи и без этого не
so-called space station
было бы э космической станции так
there used to be a Russian one there mir
называемой там раньше был российская там
yes now there is an international
мир да сейчас там международная
space station they lift these uh let's
космическая станция они поднимают вот
say ships with the help of Russian
ээ скажем корабли с помощью российских
engines in fact once again
двигателей на самом деле ещё раз ещё раз
let's say this and what and what wait have we finished I had
давайте так причём причём подождите
these engines back in the
договорили меня эти двигатели ещё были в
USSR their huge reserves got it let's take it
СССР их огромные запасы понял давайте
apart again that means Elon Musk's Space X
ещё ещё раз разберу значит Space X Илона
doesn't use Russian engines
Маска не используют российские двигатели
I don't know I haven't delved into this question
я не знаю я не вникал в это вопрос
maybe they do who uses well can
возможно используют кто кто использует
you give me an example that in order to
ну можете сказать пример для того что
lift a satellite in order to
для того чтобы поднять спутник то чтобы
lift a satellite there you need less
поднять спутник там нужно меньше
load and if something is
нагрузки а если что под более тяжёлое
needed for a heavier one a Russian engine what yes what
нужно российское двигатель что да что
Russia lifts what America lifts with
Россия поднимает что Америка поднимает
Russian engines
российскими двигателями
well  Google it please if you have No, well,
ну загуглите пожалуйста если у вас Не ну
you are saying this
вы вы же это утверждаете
if I google it from my
если я сейчас буду загугливать с
phone now, but I just had a simple connection with you
телефона но я у нас с вами связь
and understood everything, well, that is,
провёлся просто и всё понял ну то есть у
you have the usual Russian tactics and
вас обычная российская тактика и
say something like: "Well, I don't know,
говорить типа: "Ну я не
as you wish, fine, let it
см как вам будет угодно хорошо пускай
be," that is, with such success you can
будет" то есть с таким успехом вы можете
say that Russia exports, in short,
говорить что Россия экспортирует короче
supercomputers and microcircuits,
суперкомпьютеры и микросхемы
no, they don't export, they export the
нет они не экспортируют они экспортируют
metals that are needed for their
те металлы которые необходимы для их
production, well, that is, raw materials,
производства ну то есть сырьё
raw materials, of course, I understand, so let's except for
сырьё конечно понял так давайте кроме
these mythical engines, yes,
вот этих мифических двигателей да
Soviet ones, which everyone wants to
советских которые прямо все хотят у
take from Russia so that in Russia, for example, the
России взять чтобы в России допустим
best nuclear fleet in the whole world,
лучший атомный флот вообще во всём мире
uh, who, let's do it this way, what does Russia have a
ээ кто давайте так то что у России
nuclear fleet, which countries buy
атомный флот кто из стран покупает
Russian nuclear icebreakers,
российские атомные ледоколы
well, in order to develop the Arctic,
ну для того чтобы разрабатывать Арктику
such are needed I ask which countries
нужны такие Я спрашиваю кто из стран да
buy Russian nuclear icebreakers, I don't know, no
покупает российский атомный лидекон я не
one, I don't know the answer
знаю никто
to this question, no, no,
я не знаю ответа на этот вопрос не не то
but I don't know the answer to this question, and you
а а я не знаю ответа на это вопрос а
know why I'll say because it was a
знаете почему я скажу потому что это
Soviet topic, nuclear  icebreakers
советская тема была атомные ледоколы во
all over the world icebreakers are made on other
всём мире ледоколы делают на других
energy sources not nuclear that's all please well
источниках энергии не атомных вот и всё
Russia is better nuclear
пожалуйста ну Россию лучше атомный
nuclear because no one makes
атомный потому что никто не делает
nuclear icebreakers no one except Russia
атомные ледоколы никто кроме России не
makes nuclear icebreakers please please
делает атомные ледоколы пожалуйста
because no
пожалуйста потому что они не нужны
one needs them in Russia they invented
никому вот в России придумали в
nuclear icebreakers in the Soviet Union
Советском Союзе атомные ледоколы
for some reason yes and they make these atoms because
почему-то да и делают эти атомы потому
uh from the point of view yes of the danger when
что ээ с точки зрения да опасности при
flooding you get a contaminated area that's
затоплении вы получаете заражённый район
all the world does not use nuclear
вот и всё мир не использует атомные
icebreakers but submarines but underwater and
ледок а подводной лодки а подводно а
submarines can I clarify the same thing again again again
подводной лодке можно уточнить тоже дела
look now I have
ещё раз ещё ещё раз смотри теперь мне
submarines submarines too
подводные лодки подводные лодки тоже
Russia makes submarines nuclear submarines not
Россия делает подводные атомные лодки не
us we haven't finished we haven't finished
мы мы не закончили мы не закончили
submarines too they have diesel yes
подводные лодки тоже у них дизельные да
no I don't know submarines I don't know you
нет не знаю подводные лодки не знаю
know and their quantity and their quantity
знаете а их количест а их количество
what compared to Absolutely I don't know
какое по сравнени с Абсолютно не знаю
absolutely I don't know but no one look no
абсолютно не знаю но никто смотрите
one in the world makes nuclear icebreakers
никто в мире не делает атомные ледоколы
except Russia no one needs them tell
кроме России никому они не нужны скажите
me at least one product that Russia
мне хоть один товар который Россия
sells to the world besides raw materials
продаёт в мир кроме сырья
well let's think let's do
ну давайте подумаем давайте
you have one  some option no I looked and did not
у вас есть какой-то вариант нету я искал
find so and who are we comparing with we do
не нашёл так а мы с кем сравниваем
not compare with anyone we say that
ни с кем не сравниваем мы говорим что
Russia exports to the world
Россия экспортирует в мир
well raw materials of course more besides raw materials well
ну сырьё конечно больше кроме сыря ну
if raw materials then it turns out that you are a raw materials
если сырё то это вы получается сырьевая
state a raw materials appendage this is the lowest
государство сырьевой придаток это низшая
stage of economic development nothing
ступень развития экономики ничего
like that yes the sale of raw materials is the lowest
подобного да продажа сыря - это низшая
stage but processing and obtaining
ступень а вот переработка да и получение
additional value I do not remember I do not
дополнительной стоимости я не вспомню не
argue with you processing of raw materials and finished
спорю с вами переработка сырья и готовая
finished product - this is of course more interesting
готовый продукт - это конечно интереснее
than raw materials yes then I want to hear what
чем сырьём да то я вот хочу услышать что
besides raw materials Russia sells to the world what it
кроме сырья Россия продаёт в мир что она
does really what the world is
такое делает действительно что миру это
interested in it is profitable and the world buys it it is
интересно выгодно и мир покупает
not as much as we would like
это это не так много как бы хотелось бы
in fact Yes so if not so much
на самом де Да так что если не так много
at least that I am
хотя бы что
not ready to answer this question now
не готов сейчас ответить на этот вопрос
maybe phones computers some
может телефоны компьютеры какие-то
cars well what does it sell to the world what what
автомобили ну что продаёт в мир что что
you list does not apply to Russia so so
вы перечислите к России не относится так
and what approximately well rake what does
так а что примерно ну грабли что продаёт
Russia sell to the world military equipment what well
Россия в мир военную технику какую
I do not know what it buys in the same
ну я не знаю что покупает в том же самой
Saudi Arabia I do not know ask
Саудовская Аравия я не знаю спросите у
them what what is bought who  what
них что что покупается кто что
Russian military equipment does Saudi Arabia buy
российского покупает Саудовская Аравия
ask them they
из техники военной спросите у них они
No so you tell me you said military
Нет так ты же скажи ты же сказал военная
equipment I think that they buy at
техника я думаю что они покупают как
least equipment related to air defense what kind of
минимум технику связанную с ПВО какую
firearms what kind of
огнестрельное оружие какую какое
firearms Saudi Kalashnikovs
огнестрельное оружие судовско калаши
buy of course and what not-that's it and what not-that's
покупают конечно а что нет-то
it you came up with what it is better understood
нет-то вы придумали что это лучше понял
came up with what in short look so let's do it
придумали что короче смотри значит давай
Kalashnikov yes it is still Soviet old uh
так калаш да это ещё советский старый ээ
and as they show modern combat yes no
и как показывают современный бой да
one uses it anymore only those
никто его уже не использует только
downtrodden African countries
забитые вот эти там африканские страны
there where there are still stocks of this
там сили где остались запасы этого
weapon that's all no Saudi
оружия вот и всё никакая Саудовская
Arabia does not buy these there
Аравия не покупает вот эти там
Russian and modifications you don't know them
российское а модификации вы их не знаете
modifications you don't know modifications of the
модификации вы не знаете модификации
machine gun modifications super modifications
автомата модификации супер модификации
but for some reason in the world it is not
но в мире почему-то его новое не
used new buys well well okay well okay okay yes
используют покупает ну ну ладно ну ладно
what Saudi
хорошо да то что покупает ээ Саудовская
Arabia buys uh I don't know maybe it
Аравия какие не знаю может там Армата
buys Armata well the same S400 the same the
покупает ну те же самые S400
same planes of course
те же самые те же самые самолёты конечно
what planes Saudi Arabia
какие самолёты Саудовской Аравия
buys from you  and in what quantity
покупают у вас и в каком количестве
can you say well you google it and
можете сказать ну вы загуглите и
see no so you
посмотреть нет так выж вы же это
claim this well you are on the computer
утверждаете ну вы за компьютером
please I am not on the computer I can not
пожалуйста я не за компьютером я не могу
google I can not
нагуглить я тоже не могу сейчас
google it now either see that is you
нагуглить видите то есть вы
you are bol you are bol you say that Russia does not
Вы бол Вы бол Вы говорите что Россия
produce anything this is a lie I did
ничего ничего не производит это вранёт я
not say that it does not produce anything but what
не сказал что ничего не производит а что
it produces I said wrong I asked
оно производит я не так сказал я спросил
you what Russia sells to the world besides raw materials I have
вас что Россия продаёт в мир кроме сырья
another question for you no no you are
у меня к вам другой вопрос нет нет вы вы
now running away from the basics look we
сейчас убегаете от основ смотрите мы
discussed that Russia is a raw materials
разбирали что Россия есть сырьевым
traitor
предатком
for Let's fix it like this fix it you
за Давайте так фиксируем фиксируем вы не
can not yes fix it you can not
можете да фиксируем вы ничего не можете
say anything that Russia produces that
сказать что Россия производит такого что
it sells to the West everything let's now
она продаёт на Запад всё давайте теперь
you have your question here and my question is very
вы ваш вопрос вот а мой вопрос очень
simple here and how do you
простой вот а как вы
think Zelensky was corrected to sell all the
считаете вправили Зеленский продать все
subsoil of the land of Ukraine does he have
недры земли Украины имеют ли на это
such opportunities and powers to do this no he
такие возможности и полномочия нет он не
cannot sell because according to the constitution the
может продать потому что по конституции
subsoil of the earthlings belongs to the people of Ukraine
недры землян принадлежат народу Украины
he cannot sell them uh to someone we have
он не может продать их ээ кому-то у нас
no concept of selling yes subsoil and why does he
нету понятия продажи да недр а почему
do this where does he do well in  at the
это делает где делает ну вот в данный
moment he is leading to this, that he is leading to
момент он к этому и ведёт что ведёт
sell all the subsoil of Ukraine where have
продать все недры Украины где такое
you heard of such a thing are you kidding about the amount of
слышали вы что прикалываетесь в размере
50% mo no stop stop stop no no no
50% мо нет стоп стоп стоп нет нет нет
show show show the text show the text of
покажи покажи покажи текст покажи текст
this agreement I what do you want 50% everything
этого договора я что тебе го 50% все
show no show look you now
покажи нет покажи вот смотри ты сейчас
just show now yes where am I Okay you
просто покажи сейчас да где я Хорошо ты
read the draft agreement just for the sake of interest
читал проект договора вот ради интереса
just bending over just no about just
просто нагибает просто нет про просто
say here is the text you read here oh what is
скажи вот текст ты читал вот э что
being sold 50% of the subsoil don't hurry don't
продаётся 50% недр не торопись не
hurry you you look no you you will now
торопись ты ты смотри нет ты ты сейчас
pile on you again you haven't read the text of the
навалишь ты снова ты не читал текст
agreement have you read the Russian news about
договора ты читал новости российские об
this text yes show me where in the text of the
этом тексте да покажи мне где в тексте
draft even the agreement says about
проекта даже договора говорится про
selling 50% or are you going before you
продажу 50% или идёшь раньше ты
told before you ra everything means you are
рассказывал раньше ты ра всё значит
going
идёшь
hello
здравствуйте
Hello
Здравствуйте
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky and you are a young
я из города Хмельницкий а вы молодой
man where are you from well let's
человек откуда
say not young anymore but I am from
ну допустим уже не молодой но я из
Samara I
Самара
understood what brought you to chat roulette yes I have been
понял что вас привело в чат рулетку
talking for days I
да с дни разговариваю
understood
понял
let's talk ask the topic
давайте поговорим задавайте тему
well about what would the Russians  the Ukrainians did not
ну о чём бы россияне украинцы не
talk about the event, here is the court,
разговаривали с событием вот суд же
and what is there to discuss, everything is clear,
а что там обсуждать там всё понятно
Ukraine conducted a successful special operation for
украина провела успешную спецоперацию на
7 months to delay and
протяжении 7 месяцев по оттягиванию и
destroy Russian troops from the Donetsk
уничтожению российских войск с донецкого
direction, from the
направления с
Kharkov direction, a brilliant operation, they entered the
харьковского гениальная операция зашли
territory of the Russian Federation,
на территорию Российской Федерации
they showed what is possible, they showed that there are no
показали что можно показали что нет
red lines, the task was to hold
красных линий задача была удержать месяц
this territory for a month, yes, they held it for 7 months,
эту территорию да удержали 7 месяцев
generally cool, well done, yes, and why, mm, why, well, for
вообще круто молодцы да а зачем мм зачем
example, the Russians also
ну например россияне же тоже там
entered the Gostomel airport there,
заходили в Гостомельский аэропорт
they held it in Kherson, they entered and then left,
удерживали в Херсон зашли а потом ушли
yes, here is Ukraine, I explain why, the point is
да вот Украина объясняю зачем дело в том
that Ukraine left, uh, Sudzha according to
что Украина оставила ээ Суджу по
agreements, yes, according to the deal signed
договорённостям да по сделке подписанной
with Trump, yes, Trump said that as part of a
с Трампом да трамп сказал что в рамках
goodwill gesture, Ukraine is withdrawing troops
жеста доброй воли Украина выводит войска
from Sudzha and Russia will continue, where was this
из суджи и дальше Россия будет это где
written, when was this written, where was it written in the
это когда было написано это где в
Istanbul agreements,
стамбульских соглашениях ещё было
and what was written when the Istanbul agreements were
а что когда стамбульские соглашения были
already the Ukrainians, no, don't look at this,
уже украинцы были нене не смотри по это
3 days ago in A, oh, in Istanbul, they
3 дня назад в А ой в Стамбуле с
met with Erdogan and decided, yes, it
Эрдоганом встречались да и постановили
was  Mark Rubio Erdogan and Zelensky
да был Марк Рубио Эрдоган и Зеленский
what did they decide they decided that
что они решили они решили что
Putin asked that he wants a ceasefire
Путин попросил что он хочет перемирия
but he somehow feels very uncomfortable that uh
мира но ему как-то очень неудобно что ээ
he can't show his voters
он не может своим показать избирателям
his failure that they
свою несостоятельность что 7 месяцев не
can't recapture the Kursk region for 7 months then they
могут отвоевать Курскую область тогда
proposed the option that Ukraine
предложили такой вариант что Украина
withdraws its troops it
выводит свои войска она же спокойно
left calmly but no one was
вышла да никого ни в плен нету
captured where are these hundreds captured
захваченных где эти сотни захваченных в
where are a bunch of women they left in an organized manner and so how
плен где куча женоте организованно вышли
over 10,000 soldiers
да и су ну как свыше 10.000 солдат
were blocked in the Sumy show show
заблокировали в су вс покажить покажите
show what 10,000 there weren't that many there a
покажите каких 10.000 там не было
limited contingent
столько там ограниченный контингент
today today
сегодня сего
today the trial wasn't in court there were
сегоднягодня суд же был не в суд же было
1.88 people on the list 1.48 yes everything is
1.88 человек по списку 1.48 да вот все
fine they went to the territory of the Sumy
нормально вышли на территорию Сумской
region and what did they say yes everything is now the
области да и что сказали да всё теперь
ball is in Russia's court Putin
мячик на стороне Росси путин же Путин
came to the Kursk region
приехал в Куртскую область
took pictures they gave him guarantees that they
пофотографировался ему дали гарантии что
wouldn't cover him with hazel you understand they gave a
его не накроют орешником понимаете дали
guarantee this is a deal because yes
гарантию это договорничок потому что да
Ukraine is organized  she left and Sudzhi
Украина организованно отошла и суджи
kept her there for 7 months and exchanged her yes
продержав там 7 месяцев и обменяв её да
at the auction here I explain to you today
на торгах вот я тебе объясняю сегодня
Trump asks Putin there is a video about this
Трамп просит Путина есть видео про это
yeah Putin be so kind as to release 10,000
угу путин будь добр отпусти 10.000
Ukrainian soldiers don't kill them
украинских солдат не убивай их
please Putin is in a rage now what to
пожалуйста путин сейчас в раздубе что
do Putin Trump show me the video of
делать путин Трамп покажите мне видео
Trump now type it into Google no no
Трампа ты сейчас забей в Google нене у
we don't have Google they blocked release the
нас гугла нет заблокирова отпустить
Ukrainian soldiers type it into Google and you do
украинских солдат набей в Гугле и тебе
it man you asked for it yourself now
это мужик ты сам напросился сейчас
now okay
сейчас хорошо
now maybe there really is such a thing this is
сейчас может действительно есть такое
today this is today in this really
это сегодня это сегодня в этом реально
really now yes really and you say no
реально сейчас да реально а ты говоришь
one was
никого там не
blocked there something Erdogan told you something
заблокировали что-то Эрдоган что-то вам
since January yes you'll beat them up and there are
сказал с января месяца да выбоиш и
no agreements about anything I'll
никаких договорённостей о чём-то нету
go check
пойду чек
come on yeah
давай ага
[music]
[музыка]
honestly
честно
there he asks to pardon them and let them go let's
там просит помилувать их и отпустить
look now
давай сейчас посмотрю
so let's ask
так
Google now let's ask
у Гугла сейчас спросим давай
okay Google please tell me uh did you
о'кей google скажи пожалуйста ээ
contact me where are you going I'm going to
обратился ли это ты куда дедходишь я иду
smoke no no no  come back come back so that we
курить нене не вернись вернись чтобы мы
can listen I'm here here here not so that I can
послушали я здесь здесь здесь не чтобы я
see you I well I'm here otherwise tell me
тебя видел я ну я здесь а то скажешь мне
Google I hear yes Google tell me did
Google я слышу да Google скажи обращался
Trump contact Putin so that he would release
ли Трамп к Путину чтобы он выпустил
10,000 Ukrainian troops and
10.000 украинских военных и суджи
blocked Sudzhi and not shoot I
заблокированных и не расстрелял
answer nothing like that Trump did not say and
отвечаю ничего такого Трамп не говорил а
Ukrainian troops withdrew from Sudzhi according to the
украинские войска отошли из суджи по
Istanbul agreements there it was
стамбульским соглашентям там
agreed that Ukraine withdraws troops
договорились что Украина выводит войска
from Sudzhi Kadyrov Putin and Russia withdraws
из Суджи кадыров Путина а Россия выводит
troops from Ukraine
войска из Украины
oh do you see how it is your Ukrainian No no no
о видишь как это ваши украинские Нет нет
Google said look agreed
нет google сказал смотри договорились
Istanbul agreements Ukraine withdraws
Стамбулские соглашения украина выводит
troops from Sudzhi Kadyrov Putin and Russia
войска из Суджи кадыров Путина а Россия
withdraws troops from
забирает войска из
Hello where are you from I'm
Здравствуйте вы откуда
from Moscow I understand and what are you talking about it
я из Москвы понял а чем общаетесь
doesn't work out to talk about
не получается пообщаться
what you want to talk about but about something
о чём хотите пообщаться а вот о чём-то
calm I don't want to argue with anyone I
спокойном я не хочу ругаться ни с кем
understand let's talk why did Russia
понял давайте пообщаемся почему Россия
attack Ukraine
напал на Украину
and now you immediately start well why
и вот сразу начинаете вы ну почему
Russia and why not argue like that well
Россия а почему так не ругаться ну
talk calmly defends its
пообщаться спокойно защищает свои
political interests and what
политические интересы а какие
exactly well for example so that
какие конкретно ну например чтобы
Ukraine did not become anti-Russia,
Украина не стала антироссией
specify, stopped, more precisely, to become, well,
уточните перестала точне становиться ну
how did Ukraine become
что конкретно почему Украина стала
anti-Russia, specify, what exactly, why did Ukraine become
антироссией что такое Украина стала
anti-Russia, what does Ukraine become anti-Russia, what do you mean by this
антироссией что вы вкладываете в этот
term, well, you do not live in your own country, but you live in
термин ну вы живёте не своей страной а
everything, as if against Russia
вы живёте всё как что против России
specifically, we
конкретно мы живём в своей я правильно
live in our own, do I understand correctly, we
понимаю мы живём в своей стране да да вы
live in our own country, yes, you live in
живёте в Украине в своей стране то а
Ukraine, in your own country, then what does this have to do with you at all, what does this have to do
причём тут мы к Украине да ну антироссия
with us, to Ukraine, yes, anti-Russia, we live in our own country, yes, yes, we do not interfere with you, so why did you attack us,
к вам не лезем так то зачем вы на нас
defending your political interests, once again, well,
защиту своих политических интересов ещё
you say anti-Russia, how did it
раз ну ты ска антироссией как
manifest itself that we became anti-Russia, we did not interfere with you, yes, you did not interfere with
проявлялось что мы стали антироссией мы
us, and I did not Wait, stop, stop, stop, stop, that is, you interfered with us, and we did not interfere with you, but
вы к нам лезли а мы к вам не лезли но
we are to blame, I did not understand, well, tell me
виноваты мы ни понял а ну расскажи ещё
again, and I did not say that you did so, but
раз а я и не говорил что вы к нам так а
tell me what anti-Russia is, and Ukraine
расскажи что такое антироссия и Украина
became,
стала
I think you understand, you
я думаю вы понимаете просто сейчас
are just asking now to hear from  me this and
спрашиваете чтобы услышать от меня это а
you understand I don't understand no you
вы понимаете я не понимаю нет ты
came up with this term Ukraine has become
придумал этот термин украина стала
anti-Russia specifically how does this
антироссией конкретно в чём это
express itself I want to understand what's in your
выражается я хочу понять что у вас в
heads that you attacked us come on what will you give
головах что вы напали на нас давай в чём
up now
сейчас сольёшься
if you want to give up on me for the sake of your
если вы хотите меня слить ради своего
stream or will you give up now you will give
стрима или ты сейчас сольёшься ты
up now okay okay if
сольёшься сейчас о'кей хорошо если
you just enjoy giving up on me to the viewers
просто вам кайф меня слить на зрителей
okay that's it let me give up explain
хорошо всё давайте я слился объясни
explain what anti-Russia is you yourself
объясни что такое антироссия вы сами
understand what it is I'm sure that I don't
понимаете что это я уверен что я не
understand I don't understand we can we can
понимаю не понимаю мы можем мы можем
understand different things in general I don't understand
понимать вообще разные вещи я не понимаю
how we are anti-Russia if we lived with us the
как мы антироссия если мы жили смо нам
opposite Russia we want to be with Europe
наоборотник Россия мы хотим с Европой
we don't want to have anything in common
быть мы не хотим вообще ничего общего
with Russia at all we have done everything to be
иметь с Росси всем сделали всё чтобы
Russia everything we are not Russia so what are
быть Россия всё мы не Россия да так в
we in what are we anti-Russia that you
чём мы в чём мы антироссия что вы на нас
attacked us explain you've already screwed up okay let's give
напали объясняй ты уже облажался хорошо
another version no come on
давайте другую дам версию нет давай
anti-Russia explain and let's give those
антироссия объясни а давай те
official version just protection no no come on
официальную дам версию просто защиту нет
why why not come on like that you're
нет давай почему почему нет давай так ты
running away you said with your mouth yes what
убегаешь ты сказал своим ртом да что
because Ukraine has become and  anti-Russia and
потому что Украина стала и антироссией и
so that it does not become anti-Russia what do you
чтобы не ставала она антироссией что ты
mean this is anti-Russia we
имеешь в виду это антироссия мы что
attacked Russia no we on the contrary do not
нападали на Россию нет мы наоборот не
want anything in common with Russia we want to
хотим ничего общего с Россией мы хотим
be with Europe
быть с Европой
and did I ever say a word somewhere that you
а я хоть слово где-то сказал что вы
attacked Russia or wanted to attack
нападали на Россию или хотели напасть на
Russia you said that we became
Россию ты сказал что мы стали
anti-Russia I ask how this
антироссией я спрашиваю в чём это
manifests itself can it be simple if
проявляется можешь это же просто если у
you have minimal rudiments of IQ you would have
тебя есть минимальные зачатки IQ ты бы
named once 2 3 4 bitterness towards Russia
назвал раз 2 3 4 озлобленность к России
how this manifests itself how it manifests itself
в чём это проявляется в чём проявляется
yes well how it manifests itself how for example Nalyaku for
да ну как это в чём например Наляку вот
example and what does Russia have to do with it and who are the
например а при причём тут Россия
Muscovites these are Russian soldiers
а Моски это кто это российские солдаты
and in the fourteenth year also Russian
а а в четырнадцатом году тоже российские
soldiers were on the Maidan this
солдаты были на Майдане это ещё ни Крыма
was not yet Crimea or Donbass again again again again
не было ни Донбасса ещё раз ещё раз ещё
since the time of the Russian Empire
раз со времён Российской империи
Russian soldiers are called
российских солдат называется называют
Yes he also called it that look also in Taras
Да называл ещё так посмотри ещё в Тарас
Shevchenko
Шевченко
wrote Russian soldier
писал российский солдат
Taras Shevchenko yes and Russians are
тарас Шевченко да а русские - это
Muscovites
московиты
and imperial soldiers
а солдаты имперские
no comes from the name of the city  Moscow
нет происходит от название города Москвы
being an image of ethnochronym this is where you
являясь образом этнохронимом это где ты
read on Wikipedia write soldier
читаешь на Википедии напиши солдат
okay yeah
о'кей угу
among Jews are co-existent ethnonym of Russians
среди евреев колициальны этноним русских
linguistic expressions of ethnostereotype
языковые выражения этностереотипа
economy in old Russia Moscow with a
экономица в старой России Моск с
shade of disdain called Russian
оттенком пренебрежения назвали русских
people in general residents of the southern regions
людей вообще жители южных областей
Poles and Ukrainians
поляки и украинцы
what is old Russia well for example
что такое старая Россия ну например
imperial Russia not What is old
имперская Россия не Что такое старая
Russia Russian sources could
Россия Русские источники могли
use this word to designate
употреблять это слово для обозначения
residents and natives of Moscow no
жителей и уроженцев Москвы нет
look residents of Moscow and Muscovites Russians
смотри жители Москвы и москвичи русские
are Muscovites Muscovites pi yes and mo -
- это московиты московиты пи да а мо -
these are specifically Russian soldiers
это конкретно солдаты российские
yes here at the very end I found this
да воттут вот в самом конце я нашёл это
about the army that in the 15th - 10th centuries the word was
про армию что в XV тире X веках слово
also used to mean soldiers of the
использовалось также в значении солдат
Russian army depending on their
русской армии в зависимости от нического
origin also to designate
происхождения также для обозначения
Russian officials and Great Russian
российских чиновников и великорусских
merchants okay now look let's
купцов о'кей теперь смотри давай так
say in Ukraine yes on the Maidan they shout
допустим в Украине да на Майдане кричат
at Gilyak even if it is at Russians
на Гиляку даже если это на русских
what does the attack on Ukraine have to do with it well here  they
причём тут нападение на Украину ну вот
shout at Lyaka and that its
кричат на Ляку и что
somehow unimportant and that its somehow
неважительно как-то и что как-то
disrespectful so what and why are you
неуважительно ну и что а зачем вы
killing people yano its just
убиваете людей яно просто по-человечески
unpleasant as a human being well so unpleasant sit and
неприятно ну так неприятно сидите себе и
wash your face like there are troubles so
умывайтесь типа там неприятностями так
youre not bodies to wash your face no no Yes
вы же не телы чтобы умываться вылы нет
you are those yes thats why now the cities are being
не Да вы те да поэтому сейчас города
bombed look you are you Yes we are bombing you
бомбёт смотри вы вы Да мы вас бомбим
look the Moscow region is even being bombed
посмотри Московскую область даже бомбят
and thats it and those cant do anything
и всё и те ничего не можете сделать
more than that look you Putin you
больше того смотри вы Путина вы ничего
cant do anything youve never in your life yes
не можете сделать вы никогда в жизни да
you have uh a huge country with gas oil
у вас ээ огромная страна с газом нефтью
diamonds gold yes and you live like no well we live better than you by the way no you live
алмазами золотом да а живёте как не
like how much is your salary and Im studying
ты как сколько у тебя зарплата а я учусь
no salary how many scholarships do you have I do
нет зарплаты сколько у тебя стипендий у
nt have a scholarship
меня стипендии нет
and I live you live you live in the
а у меня вот живёте вы живёте вы в
richest country because Putin is
богатейшей стране потому что вас Путин и
in your mouth and in your mane thats all because
в рот и в гриву вот и всё потому что
because look Ill tell you what
потому что смотри я тебе вот что скажу
youre an ordinary
ты обычный
little one youve achieved nothing in life
мелкий ты ничего не добился в жизни
nothing  so yes you at school you
ничего не значишь да тебя в школе тебя
classmates yes not a single girl gives you
одногруппники да тебе не даёт ни одна
in short yes and you go out on
девочка короче да и ты выходишь в
chat roulette - this is the only place with a
чат-рулетку - это единственное место с
bad camera where you can sing yes
плохой камерой где ты можешь поваться да
because yes you go out and you immediately
потому что да ты выходишь и ты сразу
become a geopolitician yes you sublimate
стаёшь геополитиком да сублимируешь туда
everything there how classmates poured on you
всё как тебя на тебя нали одногруппники
yes how girls made fun of you yes
да как тебя ээ постебали с тебя девочки
you even in any case you didnt have you dont have a
да у тебя же даже по-любому у тебя не
single condom
было у тебя нет ни одного презерватива
at home not a single one thats a fact bring them to me
дома ни одного того это факт мне их
what come on come on Ill
принести что давай давай я тебе их
bring them to you you then you on your knees now on
пронесу ты то ты на коленях сейчас на
your camera on your stream you kneel down
свою камеру на свой стрим становишься на
saying that youre not on your knees no
колени говоришь что ты не на колене нет
but if I say that you
но если я скажу что ты
No you kneel down and say
Нет ты становишься на колене и говоришь
to yourself not without knees without knees on your
про себя не без колен без колен на
knees and say to yourself no well on your
коленях и говоришь про себя не ну на
knees no if you have I tell you well I wo
колени не если у тебя есть я тебе говорю
nt kneel down but so that I say so
ну на колени не встану но чтоб скажу так
no what you about yourself Yes yes yes about yourself yes
не что ты про себя Да да да про себя да
no I dont believe you everything everything everything the rear
нет я тебе не верю всё всё всё тыл
you see  you've lost it you've lost it I'm losing it now you're
видишь ты слился ты слился я сейчас ты
trying now
сейчас пытаешься всё
you see everything you your no you
видишьте твой нет ты давай всё нет твой
come on everything no your father you see because you backed out you
отец видишь потому что ты дал заднюю ты
said: "I'll bring it now" I agreed
сказал: "Я сейчас принесу" я согласился
you set the conditions I agreed and
ты поставил условия я согласился и
now you've failed if I bring it now will you say will you say
теперь ты срезался если я сейчас принесу
about me that I Yes no I'll say about myself well I'm just saying
я про себя скажу ну просто я же говорю
on my knees I won't get up yes well there is oh
на колени я вставать не буду да ну есть
okay wait wait
ой о'кей подождёшь подождёшь
they're behind this wall
они вот за этой стенкой
okay yeah
о'кей да
anyway I still feel like
вообще всё равно чувствую себя как будто
I've lost because I
бы я проиграл потому что что-то я бли
went somewhere somewhere to prove something
куда-то ходил что-то доказывал
else to you in the camera something somehow
ещёка тебе в камеру что-то как-то всё
anyway as if I've lost after all
равно как будто бы я проиграл
you don't have any condoms these are
всё-таки нету у тебя презиков нет вот
condoms or chewing gum these are chewing gum yes for a
это презики или жвачки это жвачки да по
ruble
рублю
then show me the Durex brand I
то презерватив покажи фирму дюрекс я же
showed you
показал
damn well all the way but progni
блин ну всёл даль а вот прогни же
wait
подожди
what are you anals now now
что тебя анальзы сейчас сейчас
[music] it
[музыка]
turns out it was right what do you think I'm
получается было верно ты что думаешь я
really in front of you  would get down on his knees and
реально перед тобой бы вставал на колени
say: "You're not a man, you just
сказал: "Ты не мужчина ты просто
understand, you've spread it around, in short, who the hell are you
понимаешь развестил это короче блин
really, do you understand, spread it around,
реально ты кто ты понимаешь развести
give me another 10 bucks, in short, and I'll
давай мне ещё скинь короче 10 баксов и я
get down on my knees to you, bazaar, you
тебе встану на колени базару ты ты
first understood that you would go anyway,
сначала понял что будешь всё равно пошёл
and then you came and made excuses, damn, well,
а потом пришёл и ещё оправдывался блин
I feel like I lost, you understood
ну я чувствую как я проиграл ты понимал
that you were really offended, damn, well, damn,
что ты реально обиженный блин ну блин
and you showed it anyway, come on,
ещё и показал всё равно давай
anti-Russia, come on, Avil,
антироссия давай
he has three from a pack, that is,
так Авиль у него трина как из пачки то
he bought a pack for three pieces, but he didn't
есть пачку он купил на три штуки но ни
use any of them,
одного не использовал
subscribe to
подпишись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
Telegram right now, os in, and popik, this is very, very important, YouTube is driving us through the shadow ban, and a lot of videos are not shown to people, information about streams is not shown at times, so that we have a quick connection, subscribe right
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
now  and the priest there in telegram okmdeo
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
also has interesting and useful information and we are
теж є цікава и корисна інформація и ми
obliged to maintain constant
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational communication with you regardless of what
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
YouTube will show you about this glory of
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube слава
Ukraine subscribe
Україні підпишись